F
Fi
Fix
Fixe
Fixed
Fixed &
Fixed & S
Fixed & Sy
Fixed & Syn
Fixed & Sync
Fixed & Synce
Fixed & Synced
Fixed & Synced b
Fixed & Synced by
Fixed & Synced by b
Fixed & Synced by bo
Fixed & Synced by boz
Fixed & Synced by bozx
Fixed & Synced by bozxp
Fixed & Synced by bozxph
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. E
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. En
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enj
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjo
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy T
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy Th
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The F
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Fl
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Fli
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flic
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.
'Ekta Nagar, Bareilly.'
Of all the houses in
this neighborhood, the most unique...'
'...or, you can say the most
amusing is Mishra Sadan.'
'Because here the
morning is not normal.
The evening is not normal
'Nor are the people normal.'
Shushila...
Where is my cigarette?
Last night there was one left
in the packet. Now it's disappeared!
Oh, God...
I can't take a dump without it.
And, I've to make an urgent
delivery to Bijoriya today.
If I don't freshen up now and suddenly
the pressure increases on the way...
I'll be in big trouble.
Go ask Bitti for a cigarette.
Tell her it's urgent.
How would Bitti have a cigarette?
She smokes!!!
go-go...
This was the only thing
missing in her life now.
- God save us from such a daughter.
- Just wait and watch...
Soon, you'll find bottles
of country liquor.
Bitti! Still sleeping!!
Wake up.
What are you doing, sweetheart?
Get up! queen of sweetheart
what mummy!! it was such a nice dream.
That's all you do.
Bitti!
What?
- Do you have a cigarette?
- Huh!
Since when did you start smoking?
- Your father wants one.
- I don't smoke.
Don't lie.
If you have one. Give me it me now!
I said I don't smoke.
Wanna bet.
Your father has to go to Bijoriya.
- He can't take a dump.
- What can I do?
He will be big trouble
if he has to go on the way.
I'll go and ask someone.
I knew it... you only
stole my cigarette.
Scream a little louder. The pressure will
increase, it will happens on it's own.
- Uncle, papa needs one urgently.
- I've only one, dear.
It's OK.
Where's Papa?
Any luck?
Here you go.
Thank you, Bitti.
- Wash your hands.
- But, I didn't take a dump.
Doesn't matter.
- I drank that water.
- I'm only washing my hands.
'This is Bitti Mishra.'
'Daughter of Mrs. Sushila Mishra.'
'And son of Mr. Narhottam Mishra.'
'After all,
he has raised her like a son only.'
'Sushila Mishra... teaches
children at Narmada Primary School...'
'...what Bitti Mishra
never learned in her life.'
Always listen to your elders...
'And Narhottam Mishra's words...
...are sweeter than his sweets.'
- Isn't shanu my daughter too?
what if you run out
of sweets at her wedding...
...won't I feel humiliated as well?
Son, add 5 more kilos.
I'll be right back.
Bitti, who is this crow?
He's not a crow.
He's a peacock.
Must have not taken a bath today.
- But, who is he?
- He's from our neighborhood.
My bike was out of fuel.
I asked for a lift and he obliged.
I said 'Drop me, he said okay.
Enough of that, give me 100 rupees.
I don't have.
You get a fat salary.
I bought you this
sweater from my salary right?
Take it off.
Listen, Bitti.
Sit on a motorcycle,
with both your legs on one side.
'Bitti Mishra...
never listens to advice.'
'Doesn't have too many good habits.'
'She once ate non-veg
unintentionally.'
'Now she eats at every
opportunity.'
In India it has not even released.
English films
are locally premiered...
'...at her best friend
Rama's boutique.'
'She understands only 60 percent...'
...but explains 100 percent.'
'I want to break up with you.'
I want to break you.
'Are you kidding me?'
- Have you become mad?
The electricity keeps
going in the lanes...'
'...and Bitti's tape keeps
playing without a break.'
There's a power cut in the entire city
but it will be restored soon enough.
We regret the inconvenience caused.
But there's electricity
at our neighbor's home.
Uncle, they have an inverter,
you should also buy one.
'And just not these
good for nothing boys...
'...but, the entire neighborhood
is a fan of her break dance.'
Any wedding when the DJ starts,
'...Bitti's feet start
tapping on its own.'
"Munni your anklet...
tinkles with the beat."
"Munni your bracelet...
sparkles like diamond."
"Munni... Munni..."
"Munni your anklet...
tinkles with the beat."
"Munni your bracelet...
sparkles like diamond."
"Boys can never take
their eyes off your balcony..."
"...and try to sway like you do."
"Your waist twists..."
"Your waist twists like this..."
"Mischievous eyes, vivacious body."
"When she sways, even stars
come out to play."
"Bachelors can't stop falling
in love with her attitude."
"People can't stop raving
about her grace."
"Boys can never take
their eyes off your balcony..."
"...and try to sway like you do."
"Your waist twists..."
"Your waist twists like this..."
"Twist!"
Aarush, have a sweet.
No aunty, I don't eat sweets.
Why don't both of you
speak in private, son?
Okay Aunty.
Go... Speak to him.
Go.
Our daughter Bitti works at the
Electricity board's Complaint Department.
The Complaint Department gets
hundreds of complaints every day.
But, not a single complaint
against our daughter Bitti.
It occasionally happens in parties...
...otherwise, I don't drink.
I just wanted to ask you one question.
Ask.
Are you a...
Are you... a virgin?
Virgin..?
Are you?
It doesn't matter...
But, it does matter
whether you are or not!
No, I'm not! Now?
So many boys have met her,
but they all rejected her.
There must be something
wrong with our girl.
If I try talking to her,
she gets angry.
- And you don't know how to.
- What do I do?
This is entirely your fault.
She behaves like a guy.
We should've had a boy instead.
Now where are you going?
'But there's one thing...'
'...that always bother's
Bitti's mother.'
'Bitti can't find a suitor.'
'Her engagement was canceled twice.'
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Dear... don't take your
mother too seriously.
She loves you lot.
You know she has thyroid.
Constant mood swings,
and can't stop bickering.
Papa, can I ask you something?
Everything would've been
much easier if I was a boy.
No questions asked.
"He smokes cigarettes.
But, he's a boy."
"Wanders out all night."
"But boys normally do, don't they?"
"He's a loudmouth,
but has a heart of gold."
"So what if his engagement
got canceled twice."
"He didn't like the girl."
"He just can't marry anyone."
Being a girl is a complete disaster.
Dear, that's how the society is.
I don't believe in their norms, but...
...we still have
to live in this society.
Stop... stop...
- Stop, Need a drop to the station?
- Come.
- Ticket.
- Where to?
Anywhere.
- Anywhere?
- Yes.
- Are you traveling alone, madam?
Where?
To my mother's home.
Home?
No Bindi. No Mangalsutra.
You don't look like a bride at all.
I am Christian.
Oh, Christian! Happy journey.
"The train travelling
to Jaam Nagar..."
"No..146 7 4."
"Shaheed Express..."
"...from it's actual time."
"...is delayed by two hours."
"We regret the inconvenience
caused to passengers."
Brother
Oh! Brother
Brotherrr!!!
- Yes.
- How much is that book for?
- Which one?
- The One that woke you up.
- 150 rupees.
- 150?
- Don't you have anything cheaper?
- Cheaper...
How about this one?
It's worth 80,
but I'll charge you only 60.
'Bareilly Ki Barfi.'
Fine...
I'll give it to you for 50.
Nothing less than 40,
I am sorry... No
Fine... 30.
30 rupees.
Mummy...
I am going away, Mummy.
This is the only best way to save papa
and you from all the trouble.
I am also taking along
with me 2000 rupees...
...which you had
hidden in your blouse.
Please don't try
finding the money or me!
Your headache.
Bitti...
Where do you think
you were running away, witch?
Running away from home.
Then why didn't you?
Because I can't see your happiness
You know how much
I will beat you... if..
If you're done with
'north south pole' emotional hug...
...then, make some tea for me
without sugar.
Rama. Ra...
Have you lost your mind?
Running away from home...
See, this will blow your mind away.
'Bareilly Ki Barfi.'
- Read more..
A few years ago, a
popular international...
Not the entire book.
Just read what I've highlighted.
Read this part.
"She stays in Bareilly."
"Enjoys break-dances."
"Secretly smokes cigarettes."
"Always lays a 100
rupees bet in any chat."
Oh my God... that's you!
Bareilly Ki Barfi'...Bitti.
You won't believe...
He's written things,
only you and I know about.
- Are you serious?
- Yes...
Then, he must have
written about me also.
Forget about you, and look at me.
This means... l am not the
only one who's this way.
And there's someone
in this world who thinks...
I am what I am, it's perfect
and he likes just the way I am
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
But... who's the author?
Turn.
Uff! Turn it around.
He's the author.
Pritam Vidrohi.
Do you know him?
'Now you must be thinking
this is Pritam Vidrohi.'
'No... he is not
He's the only 'Chirag'
(LIGHT) of his family.
Chirag Dubey.'
'His father wanted him
to become a doctor or engineer...'
'...and mint money.'
'Well, he's still minting...'
'But pamphlets, visiting cards,
wedding cards,..
...etcetera in his
father's printing press'
It's not 'Wets'... it's 'Weds'.
'Works hard all day...'
'...and drinking
a peg in the evening,...
...With Babli.'
'You don't see Babli.'
'Ah! There she is.'
'They say time heals every wound.'
'But his wound is still ripe.'
'Five years ago...
Babli used to be in his arms...'
'...and not just in his purse.'
'It was hard for him
to pass time without Babli...'
'...but, he was just a
time pass for Babli.'
Papa.
'At Babli's wedding,
he cried more than she did.'
'After losing the first innings...
...never mustered the courage
to play second.'
'Because he never
like anyone after that.'
'Because even today... he's trying to
find Babli in every girl.'
'The night Babli left him for good...'
'...that same night,
he took this unwavering oath...'
'...of making his
love-story immortal.'
'And his best friend
Munna read the first draft.'
Did you write this?
My tears made me.
Get your picture clicked, brother.
You'll need to publish
it with the book.
'But Chirag was a true lover.'
'If he had published the
book with his own picture...'
'...then, Babli would be humiliated.'
'If he had published
it with Munna's picture...'
'...then the book would've
been humiliated.'
'Now there only one...
'... so-called friend in the radar..'
- But, you wrote this Chirag brother.
- Yes, so?
- So how can you publish it in my name?
- Why not?
You can, but you shouldn't...
I mean... it's unfair.
Unfair is if I publish
this with your name...
...and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Look Vidrohi, you're my friend.
So, sticking to the
protocol of friendship...
...l am asking you for permission.
One more thing, boy.
Never cross paths of a rejected lover.
Or else, you'll never
find true love, get it?
- Bro, What if mother see this photo...
- Now pose...
Go on...
Ready
- Wide smile.
Smile.
'After this, in his own printing
press he secretly published...
'Bareilly Ki Barfi.'
Pritam Vidrohi ...Down-Down!
Then Pritam Vidrohi got
the beating of his life.
Mother...
- ...from the women.
- Mother...
But only in a break.
- Pritam Vidrohi ...Down-Down!
- Mother...
And before his scary dream
could come true...
Pritam Vidrohi packed
a photo of his mom...
...and fled from the
city fearing humiliation.'
'But... there was no need for that.'
'Not a single copy of
Bareilly Ki Barfi was sold.'
'The only place they were
in demand was the old paper-mart.'
'No one read it...
but definitely ate in it.'
'For the love of his friendship...'
'...Munna kept 10 copies
in his stall,...
...with due prominence.'
'The first was
copy sold in five years...'
'...which Bitti bought few days ago.'
Who is this Pritam Vidrohi?
Even Google can't find him.
ls that him?
That's Pritam-the music director.
Why are you so crazy after him?
Why shouldn't I be?
He has changed my life.
The only detail about
him is that he's from Bareilly.
But, I've never heard about him.
Look at his face...
...feels like he's
smiling under duress.
That's the shop.
Brother
- Yes.
I bought this book from here.
Books once sold will
not be taken back.
No... not... never...
I wouldn't sell it for a million.
- Huh! Did you like it so much?
- Listen...
This guy, Pritam Vidrohi...
the author.
Where can I find him?
- Why?
- Why do you care?
- Meaning?
- Just answer my question.
Where can I find him?
It says here that
he lives in Bareilly.
He used to...
But no one knows where he is now!
You wouldn't know.
Let's go.
And What if I find him?
Then you will need to find me!
Take down my address.
She wanted to know
who's the writer.
I see...
Brother, you've spent
many years in exile.
It's time to gear
up for second innings.
Leave it...
I would not leave if someone
had shown so much interest in me.
I know.
I know too! Her address!
This is your matter, brother.
You go.
Why am I going?
There's no reason for me to go.
I won't go.
No... not... never...
- Yes...
- I'm from Government Census counting.
Count yourself.
Number of people in the family.
See for yourself.
- You two... and...
- One daughter.
- Only one?
- One's enough brother.
- ls she married?
- Unfortunately not.
Why?
What do you mean?
I mean she will get married.
No doubt about it.
And whenever she does...
...get the wedding cards printed
from my brother's press.
He's got a shop close by,
around the corner.
Good Luck Printing Press.
He also prints books.
That's where Bareilly
Ki Barfi' was printed.
Are you married, son?
I am, aunty.
And soon I'll become a father.
Then, get lost.
Have you seen the
population of the country?
There is a lot of work.
Get going... Come on.
Well... I've set the stage,
and everything's in place...
...and dropped the bait as well.
The rest lies in your hands.
Let's see if you can reel her in.
But be careful.
Because It's a mad family.
It's not 'Beds' its 'Weds'.
Dumb...
Yes...
Welcome to Good Luck Printing Press.
It is supremely famous for wedding
cards, birthday cards, visiting cards...
...funerals... venerations,
rites-rituals, etc etc.
And books also?
Where did you find this?
Where can I find him?
There's no way to find him.
- You're few years too late, madam.
- He is no more?
- Well, he is no more in this city.
- I see...
Well then, phone number, email,
address... anything is alright.
- You won't get anything.
- Why not?
You see, ma'am, our company
follows a strict privacy policy.
Fans pester them a lot.
Sometimes they cut their nerve
or jump off the roof.
One of them even
swallowed rat poison.
These fans die, And then decent
people like us get stuck in between.
By the way,
what is this so important matter?
It's personal.
Anyway, thank you.
Listen...
Since... your reason is so important,
I can make an effort...
...but, only if you tell
me what was is so urgent.
- I...
- Brother card.
Your ice cream has melted completely.
Yes.
You mean to say you
are 'Bareilly Ki Barfi'.
Ditto.
How is that possible?
Exactly that's what
I want to find out.
Can you...
I can.
- English film.
- I do...
Do you understand?
Of course, if you watch
you will understand too.
This is why I want to meet Mr.
Vidrohi.
How does he know me so well?
- How would I know?
- Yes, how will you know?
Exactly.
I can't give you his
phone number and address.
And he's not on Facebook,
email, etcetera.
You know what...
...write a letter to him.
I'll deliver it to him.
And what if he replies.
I'll deliver it to you.
That's right.
Add it on my tab.
Okay brother.
Bitti is Bareilly Ki Barfi.
That's what she claims.
Oh God! Hats off to You...
What did you do?
One mango with two seeds.
One Bitti and the other Babli.
Does she know you're the author?
Are you going to tell her?
First let me find out whether
she's telling the truth.
What if it's true?
I'll give it a try.
And, what if she's lying?
- Well then, I am already in exile.
- True.
See...
If he was on Facebook
we could've have messaged him.
How about this one?
This one.
No...
I look too healthy in this one.
Why are you sending
your photo along
Just send the letter.
Well... Romeo should know
how his Juliet looks like.
How about this?
My stomach's also visible in this one.
Nice!!
Brother, even her stomach's
visible in this one.
She's advanced like
sister-in-law Babli.
What has she written in the letter?
"Dear Pritam..."
"Everyone only sees
the fault side of me."
"But, in the same faults
you saw my positives."
"l am really happy to know this."
"Even more happier that now
somewhere in this world there's...
...someone who understands me
and likes me for the way I am."
"If you ever come to Bareilly..."
"...then do meet me."
"The sweets from our
shop are also as sweet."
"Your Babli... Bitti."
Bro... she's become emotional!
You've become emotional too!
'Chirag's pen was no
longer filled with tears...'
'...but joy instead.'
'Babli was history...'
'...and a new story awaited him.'
Brother Chirag.
Tillu... make one for
brother Chirag as well.
Why did you ask me to stop?
I am in a hurry!
- But what's the hurry?
- Need to give her the letter.
Ohh...
She wrote to you yesterday and
you're sending her a reply today.
So? - Even the internet
in Bareilly isn't this fast.
You must wait for few days
before sending her a reply.
Or else you will get caught!
I see.
Did he reply?
He will.
- Yes...
- Hello, uncle.
Hello. Hello.
How can I help you?
Uncle, I own a press.
Congratulations.
I have a confectionery shop.
By the way, how much do you
charge for pressing a single shirt.
No, uncle, I own a press... 'press'.
What can I do, son?
Papa, he's Mr. Chirag.
From Good Luck Printing Press.
- Hello.
- I see... I see...
- Hello. You did tell me about him.
- Sit down.
Yes.
So what brings you here?
Well, our shop will
soon be completing 50 years.
So, is he buying our shop?
No... if we print some
golden jubilee pamphlets...
- ...we will get some publicity. Hello.
- Hello.
And uncle, I'll print
1000 pamphlets for only 500.
In golden ink... no extra charge.
- Very good.
- What's your name, son?
Chirag Dubey.
Are you married?
- No, aunty. I am still single.
- How about some juice?
Let it be, no need...
I can't let you leave just like that.
Forget her.
Print 1200 for 400 rupees.
We're like family...
it will be done.
I'll 'WhatsApp' you
when the job's done.
Just keep your 3g on.
Sushila, give him my phone number.
I don't remember it.
How can I know your number?
I don't call you myself,
how can I remember.
- Write down mine.
- Yes.
Why? He will give you a missed call
- Papa, I'll give him my number.
Take down my number.
Why don't you feed it yourself.
Okay
- Son, juice.
Thank you.
Oh, benevolent Lord.
Great.
See you, uncle.
"Stay with me...
like the hum on my lips..."
"...and I'll stay with
you like your dreams."
"Dwell in my soul... like love..."
run in the direction...
the trumpets blare."
"Hold my hands...
sweetheart, I promise."
"Now you're my desire, my intent."
"Say my name, beloved...
I am your world."
"The rains follow
you wherever you go."
"The rains follow..."
"Stay in my breath...
like the sweet fragrance."
"And... I'll pray for your grace."
"Dwell in my soul... like love..."
- Sometime talk to us also.
run in the direction...
the trumpets blare."
"Your love-letter... is still
stored in my heart, sweetheart."
"Your love-letter sweetheart."
"...l wonder what lies in my fate."
She's exactly like
sister-in-law Babli.
95%
- "...l wonder what lies in my fate."
"Stay with me..."
- Except for the mole on her back.
"...like the hum on my lips..."
I like you.
What did I do?
Actually, I've always come across
stubborn and chauvinistic type of boys.
God knows what they
think of themselves...
...and treat other women like dirt.
And me?
You...
You're like a... Libran.
Libran.
- What a lucky guess.
- You are.
I am a Libran.
- See.
- A pure Libra.
Librans always maintain a balance.
Like my father.
Always maintaining a
balance between me and my mother.
Then your birthday must be nearing!
It's closing in 23 minutes...
Today is your birthday!
Get up.
- Where?
- Get up... l said get up.
- Let's go, I'll tell you on the way.
- Why?
- Come on...
- That's expensive stuff.
Here... here...
- Lovel Sweets...
- Lovely sweets.
The 'y' fell off in the last monsoon.
Come on, we don't have much time.
How will you open the lock?
You don't have the key.
This is only to keep the thieves away.
- Are you crazy?
- Yeah... don't you know.
What are you doing?
Happy Birthday Mr. Chirag.
How is it?
Spicy.
"Stay with me like the hum on my lips...
Now?
"...and I'll stay with
you like your dreams."
"Dwell in my soul... like love..."
- Bye.
run in the
direction... the trumpets blare."
Son...
He looks okay... got a long nose.
No moles on his face either.
But even moles can be cut
off with horse's hair.
He owns a printing press,
so must be earning well too.
Also, he has a motorcycle.
Let's assume that even if his
press shuts down, then...
We still have the confectionery shop.
The least he can do
is shoo away the flies.
Isn't it?
I know what Vidrohi
writes in his letters.
I see...
So tell me, James Bond.
That you say such cute things.
You have a nice handwriting.
And whenever he opens his letter...
...he can smell your faint fragrance.
That's nothing new.
The entire neighborhood can.
Guess what do I write in the letter?
You're dying to meet him, right?
What happened?
Tell me...
I've written to him thrice...
...that I want to meet him.
But he ignores my requests.
Maybe he doesn't want to meet you.
Fine, then...
- ...I'll stop writing to him.
- Maybe he does.
I don't know.
I want to meet him only once.
I have a right to meet the
man who knows so much about me.
Isn't it?
Only you know him...
please introduce us once.
- What if you don't like him?
- Doesn't matter.
And, what if you do?
If I do, then even my
mom and dad should like him.
If they do, Hi ...otherwise, bye.
Please help me meet him once
I'll do anything you say.
please... just once.
Just once.
But, how will you make them meet?
Vidrohi ran away years ago.
Who knows whether
he's still alive or dead?
Who's introducing her to Vidrohi?
Then?
- Who's the real author of the book?
- You?
- And who wrote the letter?
So who will go to meet her?
You!
Brother, hang it on this.
Take brother.
Let's meet in the evening.
It's your turn today.
See, Bareilly Ki Barfi.
This book is messing her mind.
It says here if she smokes,
she's good.
If she watches English
films, she's sweet.
So what's wrong?
Do you want to know what's wrong?
See...
There's that boy, Chirag.
He's so well-mannered, talented.
And look at him... wretch.
Don't call him wretch.
Why not?
I would poison his juice.
Son, you?
I was passing by and
heading towards Ghanta Ghar...
...and thought I should
stop and pay you a visit.
- I'll get some juice for you.
- No, no, aunty.
I guess you guys are busy
in some kind of family discussion.
I'll leave.
Your Bareilly Ki Barfi.
- Here.
- Groundnuts.
- Thank you.
- Bless you.
On one side is the girl...
...who's head-over-heels
in love with the author.
And on the other side is her mother,
who's willing to take his life.
So what are you planning to do now?
This is love, Munna...
...it demands sacrifice.
Then chalk-out another
name in the name of love.
Don't you have any brains?
- Why?
- Whose name is on the book?
- Pritam Vidrohi.
- And the photo on the book?
Pritam Vidrohi.
So who will make the sacrifice?
Brother, your first love
made him flee from the city.
What if your second
love demands his life?
No-no... one should not
treat someone so badly.
Forget it, let's do it.
It's going to be fun.
But where is he these days?
Hello, son.
Sit down, it has been really long.
Sit, son.
Have some tea.
Aunty, no need for these formalities.
So, what brings you here?
What can I say, aunty?
I was going through my old album...
...and noticed
Vidrohi's innocent face.
And then... l really
started missing him.
Where is he these days?
He's become a big man now.
Works at a really big company, as a...
What is it called? Sales Manager.
Get it?
Those guys who sell stuff.
That's what he does now.
Wait. Look..
He gave me this ATM card.
I can withdraw any amount I want.
But I don't need it.
See... last month he sent this TV.
It's too thin,
but the image's really clear.
And this fan too.
Even in a slow speed,
you feel cold in minutes.
But where is he these days?
In Lucknow.
Patrakarpuram
- Thank you.
- Have some cashews, son.
Take it.
- Let's go, you glutton.
- I eat every day, son.
That's enough, son...
Thank you.
Why?
For everything, you're doing.
Why are you doing it?
Climb aboard, brother.
You've got our tickets.
Good bye.
See you later.
- See you later.
- Brother, the train's leaving.
Take care of yourself.
'Now, according to
Vidrohi's mother...
'...he's this successful.'
And that's not all, sir.
This 400 N/m beast comes
with six airbags, ABS...
...which is your Anti
Lock Braking system.
Fraction control...
Well, if you ask me
I think this is your car.
Good.
- I think we'll take it.
- Okay.
Pack the blue one.
'But the reality is...'
- Show that one..
- Take a look, sister-in-law.
This comes with a blouse-piece
attached to it.
There is two types of
fading in this sari.
Really.
Front and back.
See.
In fact, it's got extensive
intricate work done on the borders.
Sales Manager is selling saris.
- Should I order tea or something else?
- No.
- Do come again.
- Sure.
Congratulations for
your wedding, brother.
Come on.
Brother, do you have
anything in Chanderi?
Yes, we...
Unbelievable, dude...
You're selling saris in an age where
you should be taking them off.
Brother, you...
What are you doing here?
Order some Cola... and
we'll talk in detail.
So you won't come along?
No, brother.
Because of you... l lost my degree,
fled from my city.
I cannot afford to lose this job now.
Pritam, who's going
to look after the customers?
Get back inside.
We have a huge variety in Chanderi.
Look at the borders,
it's got a beautiful border.
You can get these in different colors.
I'm telling you,
brother, I cannot do this.
Look, brother, I've found
true love almost a decade later.
But the girl loves the
author of 'Bareilly ki Barfi'...
...and according to the book,
that's you.
That's really nice.
You created this problem,
now it's come back to haunt you.
Brother, you got to explain
him the way he understands best.
Listen...
The girl wants to meet you once.
Meet her. Break her heart.
I will make mine
Then get lost.
You find your way.
I'll find my way.
Yes... this is the border.
It's very nice.
Don't mind brother,
but can I say something...
Everything that happened
with me in the last five years...
...did it make any difference to you?
So, now I don't care whether
your heart break or aches.
Look, bro...
If I am heartbroken,
then so will be your mother.
Why mother?
When your mother finds out
that his dear, beloved, son is a liar.
And sells saris to women,
by draping them on his body.
She will be heartbroken.
- Right, Munna?
- Yes, brother.
She won't stop wailing.
This isn't right... it's blackmail.
Correct answer. And, you win a
gift voucher from your own shop.
Brother!
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
"The kid has turned stylish
and will now be menacing."
"With time his coolness
keeps Oh so increasing."
"Coolness keeps Oh so increasing."
Bitti hates chauvinists
men and bullies
She's right...
they are worth being hated.
Always bullying people around.
You must become like them.
- What?
- "The kid has turned stylish..."
- Brother, this is one's too tight.
- "...and will now be menacing."
"With time his coolness
keeps Oh so increasing."
"The simple guy's
good time sure has come."
"His super smart ways will now..."
- Yes Bro..
"...get the whole world watching."
- Hey Bro...
I can't do that.
He cannot do it, brother.
Listen to me...
I am right here to teach you.
Yes, but...
You know what,
just take me the way I am.
No one likes me anyway,
except for my mother.
She won't either.
Let's do that.
We can't take a chance now.
"With style more than
he himself could handle."
- Keep this.
- It's for me, brother.
Let's go.
- Give it here... Leave.
- Bro, gave it to me.
Should it take the call.
Yes, brother Chirag.
Curb your emotions.
Say it with attitude.
Who is this speaking?
I'll throw this sweet
corn soup on your head.
'Who is speaking?'
You call me.
My prepaid balance is low.
Brother...
Take your time.
Hello...
Go on...
"His attitude has no boundaries,
no barriers."
"Everyone better get in his good
books before he gets even bigger."
Hello...
Y... Go on...
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
"I'm not the swag...
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
Don't try to act too smart.
Otherwise....
Let's imagine someone's
calling you from the back.
How will you look?
- You mean, with attitude.
- Yes.
Call me once.
Munna.
Vidrohi.
Vidrohi!
Bullies never look back.
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
"I'm not the swag...
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
So time for your final test.
What are you saying?
This is Lucknow.
People shoot at first
sight and think later.
And I don't like sour betel-leaf.
But you must today.
I'll get one for you.
What do you think,
we're on a morning walk?
Get on your bike.
Take a long run-up...
and speed away like a bullet.
Come on.
Lift the stand.
What do you think? Can he do it?
Here.
Hey bro, why are you parking
in the middle of the road?
- Who the hell is he?
- Move your bike.
Move it... are you deaf?
- One sweet betel leaf.
- Listen.
Move your bike. What a strange guy.
- Parked his bike in the middle.
- Hey Hero...
Hey man... you
How much?
10 Rs
Move your bike,
- We can't move our car.
Come on.
Move your bike.
Get lost with your bike.
Do you think you own the road?
Move your bike.
"Coz I'm a bad...
bad Bada** babua (BOY)."
"The kid has turned stylish
and will now be menacing."
"With time his coolness
keeps Oh so increasing."
"The simple guy's good
time sure has come ."
"His super smart ways will
now get the whole world watching ."
There's a power cut
in the entire city...
...but it will be
restored soon enough.
We regret the inconvenience caused.
It's me.
ls your phone in the
Lost and found department
No.
Oh! The battery's dead.
Well, let me recharge you.
Hold my hand.
I've found Vidrohi?
Are you serious?
- How is he?
- See for yourself.
Let's go.
I'm bringing him along.
Great... see you tomorrow.
Gopal, get me some tea.
'One is not a schemer
and other is not a bully.'
'But... strange are the ways of love.'
'One's hatching schemes...
...and, the other is
emerging with an attitude.'
Yellow suits you.
- This one?
- No.
You're acting more
snooty than a heroine.
- The one you're wearing also looks nice.
- Be quiet.
- This?
- Blue buttons don't suit you.
- It's from your shop.
- Boutique.
Right... boutique.
Your phone's ringing.
Hello Madam,
You haven't left yet?
I'm just leaving.
You're really unbelievable.
You took four days to find Mr.
Vidrohi.
I can at least take
2 hours to get ready right!
Let him wait, I am coming.
(Okay.)'-
She'll be here any minute.
- I'll be fine... but, isn't this too much?
- No.
Just remember what I said.
And, brother... my voice...
From the stomach...
- Like Mr. Bachchan.
- Hello.
Hello.
Name... what was her name?
- Bitti.
- Bitti...
Dimwit... don't foil the plan.
I will try my best.
This is it.
We've arrived.
She's here.
Hi.
Hello.
It's me...
Now just repeat after me.
What can I do?
Tell him it's Vidrohi's work.
Who? Vidrohi!
If he still doesn't listen,
give him one tight slap.
And don't call me again
for such trivial matters.
Hang up...
So... what was your name?
Guddi?
- Which one is Guddi?
- It's Bitti. I'm Bitti.
Bitti... right.
- Rama. Best friend.
- Best?
Wait a minute,
how could you not recognize me.
- I sent you my photo.
- Photo.
Yeah, I sent my photo
along with the letter.
Letter?
- The one in the sari.
- Sari?
- Yes...
- Right, your photo...
- Say something.
- So many people send their pictures.
- He's a public figure.
- Yeah.
Hey...
Son, come here.
Yes, sir.
What will you have?
What, sir?
Who's going to ask
what we'll have, huh?
Sorry, sir.
What will you have?
Chow-mien for everyone.
- Okay, sir.
- No, we're leaving.
- Okay.
- But, you just got here.
We need to take Rama's
brother to the doctor.
We do, don't we?
- Yes.
- So get up.
Let's go.
- Invite him for lunch tomorrow.
- Why?
It's a Sunday.
You can introduce Mr.
Vidrohi to your parents.
It's a Sunday.
Fine, I'll meet her parents.
Okay,.
By the way, you write really nicely.
You look really nice.
- Thank you.
- Lets go.
- Okay...
- You were amazing.
- And the waiter...
- They are coming back.
Fine, then get going.
What's wrong?
Don't feel like leaving?
Sit down and eat.
- No, Thank-you, I had left my purse.
- Okay.
Wait... wait...
- I'll see you out.
- No...
- Come on.
- Let him go along.
- Let's go.
- Okay, bye.
So arrogant.
I wanted to slap him.
"Which one is Guddi?"
Who does he think he is,
Guddi's uncle.
He wasn't that bad though...
Every successful
man is a bit arrogant.
Tell me...
Have you ever heard a beggar say...
"Spare me some change...
or get lost."
Have you?
Wise guy's has even self-invited
home tomorrow.
Listen, I am coming too.
You're having this special interest?
I like him.
I am warning you...
- If he tries to act smart tomorrow...
- Then you can slap him.
Let him come home first.
What do you think?
We'll see...
Brother, when sister-in-law
is over Vidrohi...
...then why give her another dose.
Every antibiotic needs
to be taken for three days.
The effect is never
seen in the first dose.
If you don't complete the course...
...then, there's a chance
of the sickness coming back.
You mean... the next
two doses are her parents.
Why did you get this sari?
My mother always says never
go to any house without a gift.
You're not going there as a suitor.
Fine, then you can give her this.
You bought it, so you give it.
In fact, you can drape
it on yourself as well.
"See sister-in-law... it's got
three different kinds of shades."
"Front and back..."
Fine, pack it.
And no need to make a feast.
He's not coming over
to ask for marriage.
Dear daughter! I am not so lucky, that a
guy will meet and ask you for marriage.
Don't keep your hopes high.
I am going to stay right here, dancing
on your head for the rest of your life.
Go take a look, must be Chirag.
- I'll go answer the door.
- I'm going to call Rama.
- Hello uncle.
- Bless you, son. And, who are you?
Come in, uncle.
This is your home only, isn't it?
Come in... don't be shy.
- Why would I be shy?
- Hello, uncle.
First, you touched my feet
and now you're greeting me again?
- That's me.
- It's him.
- Hello, aunty.
- Hello, son.
- Chirag, who is he?
- He's my friend.
Papa, that's Mr. Vidrohi.
Remember I told you about
him yesterday.
So he's this guy who
wrote that absurd book.
I'm sure you liked it.
Happy birthday, Whenever it is!
Chanderi.
What would you like to have, son?
- Buttermilk, juice, tea, coffee.
- I'll have tea, aunty, Hot.
- And you'll have juice only!
- Yes.
Vidrohi, do you write to make
a living, or is it just a hobby.
With the grace of Goddess,
I've enough money...
...to buy your shop
and gift it back to you.
- Me?
- Writing is just a hobby.
What's wrong with your neck?
This body has grown old son...
It always needs some repair or other.
Just last week he
was cured of his piles.
It's nothing serious, uncle.
Add some basil seeds in
water and drink it at night.
- It will fix your all your problems.
- Those things don't work.
- Allow me.
- No... no...
Don't do Vidrohi.
- Let me...
- Let it be.
Don't break his neck instead.
- Leave me.
- What are you doing?
Quiet!
Hold this.
Hail Bajrang Bali!
Be gentle, son.
One..
Two... three... done.
Papa, are you alright?
Bitti, Shall I turn?
- Yes turn.
- Careful.
Wow! I can see everything
from the loo to Sushila.
Bitti, I can even
see the pots behind me.
Wow.
- Since when did you start doing this?
- Just now.
Your father's my first customer.
- Hello... call now.
- Bitti....
...give him 10-20 rupees
as a token of appreciation.
- Give him money.
- Uncle, I have a lot of money.
- Are you married, son?
- No, aunty.
I knew it.
Answer the phone.
Phone ringing
( RING TONE 'HEY LISTEN')
Hold on.
Hello.
- Listen....
- You listen up.
Next time if you call me...
...I'll kick you so hard,
you'll get a dimple on your a**
Hang on now.
Hot...
The tea is hot, son.
- We'll be leaving, aunty.
- Okay, son. You can leave.
But you stay, son. I won't let
you go without having lunch.
- I really like you, son.
- Okay.
Eat.
- They are very famous, taste it.
- I know.
In a brief moment...'
'...he turned papa's neck straight,
and turned the game around.'
I told you... send him back.
But you wanted to complete the course.
Now it's an overdose.
That was too much man!
Were you trying to be a hero?
I did exactly like you taught me.
And, what were you
saying on the phone?
You'll make a dimple on my a**
- No, I...
I was only sticking to my character.
My performance will go weak
if you keep changing the script.
Why did you have to
fix her father's neck?
An old man was in pain...
...so I thought I should fix his neck.
He is your father-in-law after all.
- I was just helping you out.
- Mr. Helping hand...
You were supposed to depress her,
but you've impressed her instead.
Fine, I'll go back then.
- Right, go on...
- You cannot leave like this.
You must first clean
up the mess you have made.
This new hairstyle really suits you.
- Have another one.
- No...
- Take it.
- I don't want it.
I've been eating since morning.
You must eat properly.
You've become so scrawny.
Will a wedding dress
look nice on this body?
All the faults are with me, right mom?
You can wear my wedding dress.
- Uncle.
- Yes dear.
Mr. Vidrohi.
Bitti... at this hour?
Yeah... If papa doesn't eat a sweet
betel-leaf after dinner he gets bitter.
What are you doing here?
Well... l have a similar habit.
If I don't eat a dessert
after dinner I get bitter too.
I see...
You should eat more sweets...
It will cure your bitterness.
- Am I that bitter?
- No...
...but, you're not like
I thought you would me.
I mean, Rama and me.
What did you and Rama think?
You see... your letters were filled
with the fragrance of romance.
But you turned out to
be the fragrance of bullies
Sol...
Don't get me wrong.
You're not that bad person.
It's the conditions
That make people bad.
You are right.
It's the conditions and
people who made me bitter.
But even bitter people have a...
Huh?
Heart... and it's not bitter at all.
Bitti...
Vidrohi, Are you okay.
Sweetmeat...
Make that two.
You didn't tell me...
did you like Vidrohi?
You never asked.
From the time he is here
you don't even miss me.
- You could've at least called.
- You could've too.
- Yes, I could.
- So...
So tell me, how did you like Vidrohi?
You know, when we met first...
- ...l wanted to claw his face.
- I knew it.
No... but, when he came home...
...l realized, he's not that bad.
And, mom and dad
are completely floored.
I see...
So, what's the plan?
What's the plan?
We've just met twice.
We'll first get to know each other.
Meet few more times.
You've met me many times.
- So?
- What do you think about me?
What's to think?
That You're my very good friend.
No one does what you did for me.
- She just friend-zoned me.
- They are here.
You're here.
Brother...
Vidrohi, Remember we
must close this chapter today.
I've by-hearted everything,
brother, don't worry.
- How are you?
- Great.
Hello.
- We're early.
- You're half an hour late.
This place is for boozing at night.
And you guys are eating groundnuts.
Yeah, right.
Looking at the way you drink...
...you would hardly have any
place in your stomach for groundnuts.
You're absolutely right.
This is exactly what I say
to myself every night when I drink.
And forget in the morning.
- He's also got memory loss.
- Yeah...
Oh yes...
And I've also been to jail
once because of this mix-up.
I see...
Oh, God... jail... criminal...
this is really serious.
It's nothing serious.
Lord Krishna was also born in a jail.
And, one should not
remember everything.
Wow...
What if I forget you tomorrow?
It's not that easy
to forget Bitti Mishra.
Let's make a bet.
And you'll definitely not forget
me until tomorrow.
- What is there tomorrow?
- What?
How can you forget?
You printed all those pamphlets.
Golden Jubilee Celebrations
of Lovely Sweets.
- How can you not come?
- He can't come.
- Why not?
- He's leaving for Lucknow tonight.
Bagh Express... Northern Railway.
- Happy journey.
- But...
Going back... Yeah, I'm going back.
How can he come?
He's leaving, he can't come.
Hold this. Show me the ticket.
I see...
And, what if it gets torn?
No, no, Bitti...
No, Bitti...
I swear I'll never talk to you again.
Return the ticket.
- Tell her.
- Yeah, I won't either.
- No chance.
- Fine, leave.
Give me your phone.
I'm low on balance.
Delete my number, and I will too.
Because you're leaving.
- Go on...
- Great.
So Mr. Vidrohi,
you've to pack your bags... and
Let's go
- Brother, keys.
- Don't be sad, Bitti.
- Doesn't matter.
Please, leave.
This is no time to get emotional,
Vidrohi.
I had a hard time getting
this ticket... through VVIP quota.
With recommendations from Mr. Vishnoi.
- Let's go.
- Bitti...
No... the trains are packed.
'Vidrohi's revolt... Fantastic.'
I can't go back breaking your heart.
'But soon he was hit...
I mean got ditched.'
- You cannot leave Bitti.
- Listen to me.
You tore up the ticket.
I like Rama, Brother. If I die,
Bitti won't wait for 14 years.
Just kill him.
I like Rama.
Bitti's my sister-in-law.
The question is whether
Rama likes you too.
Don't know.
But I tore up the ticket to find out.
I'll stay here for another
week and test her.
If she's the one for me,
then we'll leave together.
- Sorry.
- Huh!
Sorry.
There's water in this ear,
say it in this one.
- Sorry.
- Fritters...
Yes 'Lorry'
OK now you focus all
your attention on Rama.
Okay.
I will support you in this love story.
Buy a really nice gift for Rama.
- There's no need for this.
- It's love after all.
I've told you a thousand times...
...don't bathe at night.
See aunty,
He took a bath with his clothes on.
"Abracadabra...
my beloved's so handsome."
"Always dressed smartly,
whether it's Delhi or Agra."
"Your earrings make
my heart skip a beat."
"When you shake the waist,
it steals millions of hearts."
"Your earrings make
my heart skip a beat."
"When you shake the waist,
it steals millions of hearts."
"Stop taunting me...
Don't be a wise guy."
"l am not Juliet,
And you're not my Romeo."
"O Sweety..."
"O Sweety your drama,
creates a stir."
"This is unfair."
"Believe it or not,
we're crazy about you..."
"Listen O,
sweetheart, we're your beloved."
"DJ I"
"Crazy"
"Don't make a commotion..."
"...everyone's watching."
"What do you get from making a scene."
"Don't ignore me...
I am not useless."
"Teach me the language of love."
"Stop taunting me...
Don't be a wise guy."
"l am not your Juliet,
And you're not my Romeo."
"O Sweety..."
"O Sweety your drama, creates a stir."
"This is unfair."
"Believe it or not,
we're crazy about you..."
"Listen O sweetheart,
we're your beloved."
"Abracadabra... my
beloved's so handsome."
"Always dressed smartly,
whether it's Delhi or Agra."
Bravo, Mr. Mishra.
The 'Pukhraj-gem' has
started to show effect.
We were trying to
find one suitor for Bitti...
...but, now we found two.
Now, choose what you want.
And, it's not like we've
to choose between good or bad.
One's good... and the
other's a slightly better.
Both are well suited.
That's the problem.
Who do we choose?
Right?
'On one side, Mr. Vidrohi was
making his impression'
...while on the other Mr.
Chirag was breaking his head
- Hello, aunty.
- Hello-hello.
Your spectacles were broken,
weren't they? I got it fixed.
That's a big help, son.
It's hard to read anything without it.
Everything's so clear now.
Son, you care so much for everyone.
- Can I say something?
- Please do.
I've been thinking about
something for the past few days.
About Bitti's marriage.
Oh, Aunty,
Bitti is a really nice girl.
She will get married sooner or later,
don't worry.
Yeah...
Actually, I already know
who's best groom for her.
I will convince Bitti...
- And you...
- What?
You convince Vidhrohi.
- Vidrohi... for Bitti?
- Yes.
- Did Bitti say that?
- She doesn't have to.
They look like a match made in heaven.
You just be like God Hanuman
...and take this burden off my chest.
'When a lover feels
the storm in the sea.
'...he finds different ways to
save himself from loosing his love.
- What happened?
- What can I say, aunty?
- Vidrohi is a divorcee.
- Huh?
Hmm...
- Brother Chirag.
- This way, Vidrohi.
Brother...
What's wrong?
Why did you call me suddenly?
What's happening, isn't good for you.
What happened now?
That seed of love,
you sowed in Rama's heart...
...was reaped by someone else.
- What do you mean?
- It means...
Someone came to see Rama yesterday.
And they really liked Rama a lot.
Liked her?
Total.
Did Rama say yes?
She didn't say no either.
Who... who is the guy?
Tell me his name.
There's nothing you can do.
He's a goldsmith,
he's got a shop of his own.
He can melt silver,
and make jewelry for Rama.
Even his security guard makes
more money than you.
But...
I've seen love in
Rama's eyes for you.
Yeah... so did I.
In fact, I've seen it more often.
Honestly?
So, what should I do, brother?
My advice is that you
should tell her tomorrow.
- Tomorrow is also lucky Wednesday.
- Yes.
- I will if you say so.
- And, listen...
- Say it in front of everyone.
- Why?
Huh! You only kiss in private.
...but in front of everyone
you openly express your love.
You're right, brother. I will try.
And, write down a few lines,
so you can propose to her.
Have you heard
Altaf Raja's(SINGER) songs?
- You'll get lots of ideas from him.
- Okay.
Okay, brother.
What do you think, brother?
Will Rama say a yes?
Who cares?
The neighbor's kid
has climbed up the tree.
If he hikes down safely,
we'll get to eat mangoes.
And, if he falls down and dies,
we'll get to eat at his funeral.
In this situation,
whether Rama says yes or no...
Bitti is sure to get heartbroken.
Can I say something, brother?
You're such a villain.
This lake is where love was born!
The film was called 'Jawani Diwaani'.
Vinod Khanna and Dharmendra
waged a fierce war.
And the reason was
Hema Malini, mister.
- Say it.
- "Dream Girl..."
"The queen of my dreams...
Dream girl."
Turn your head that side... and
enjoy the view from this side.
- Mister.
- Yes, mister.
- Can you stay quiet, mister?
- Why, mister?
Would you like one, mister?
Why are you getting angry?
It was so much fun.
Turn your head that side...
and enjoy the view from this side.
- Mr. Vidrohi wants to say something.
- Really...
Speak LIP...
Don't be shy.
Oh no... l am not shy.
"Your heart has stolen my heart."
"And stolen my peace and sleep."
"Don't make any excuses."
"I've made up my mind
to make you my wife, Rama."
"Will you marriage me?"
"Will you marry me?"
- "Will you marriage me?"
Look... Vidrohi, you're a great guy.
- And I like you too.
- Thank you.
But, I cannot marry a divorcee.
- It's against our culture.
- You've great values.
Divorcee...
- Hold on... who's a divorcee?
- Me...
Me?
What are you saying?
I've never even been engaged.
I mean, I've never even...
You...
- Say something.
- What will he say?
He's the one who told me.
And that's Suicide Point...
Every year 72 lovers
drown to death here.
"Dreamgirl..."
Your game's up, brother!
And, I will make you pay for this.
You will have to
clean up all this mess.
- And you can tag in too.
- Stay in your limits, okay.
You mind your limits, understood.
Or else, I will really kick your a**
Sit down.
- Slap him, brother.
- Shut up.
You've turned my life into a big joke!
I've no place!
I was quietly making
a road for myself.
But you just ruined everything.
- You made me divorcee...
- Quiet!
Bitti's mother wants
to make you her son-in-law.
What else could I do? Tell me.
Helped you instead.
I did what I thought was
right at that moment, that's it.
What about my heart
that got shattered?
What about that?
Who told you to lock eyes with Rama?
Just help me get my love, and then...
...you can go anywhere you want,
I don't care.
You... you're such a selfish man.
I mean... you can ruin anyone's
life for the sake of your life.
I am done with being exploited.
I tried my best to be your friend.
Now, I will show you.
Just watch...
Tell me what you can do.
Nothing much.
I will steal Bitti
from right under your nose.
Just watch.
This hair style I gave
you is really amazing.
But, have you seen
your face in the mirror?
You can't even woo a boy.
If girls only cared about looks...
...then half of the boys in India
would've still been bachelors.
Understood.
I will take away Bitti
from you... it's a dare.
Let's imagine that you
do get married to Bitti...
...then, I'll play the
trumpet at your wedding.
And I'll decorate the flowers.
Now get lost.
Better start preparing.
Brother,
he turned out to be a traitor.
Trying to foil our plans.
Bitti will apply henna on her hands.
Not cow-dung.
There's nothing he can do.
Aunty, where is Bitti?
She is upstairs.
Chirag, come here. Sit.
Son, where does Bitti
keep wondering at nights?
She's a girl after all, not a witch.
- Why don't you talk to her?
- Don't worry, aunty.
I'll talk to her.
Just make some tea. Hot...
(Okay.)'-
How are you, Rama?
It's entirely my fault.
I shouldn't have brought
that imbecile here.
All he did was write a book...
...and now he thinks
he's Ghalib (POET)!
Thank God Rama rejected him.
Good for nothing...
Letters for you...
and proposal for Rama.
This is not the way.
You don't have to be sad, Bitti.
Why would I be sad?
He's just a divorcee
and not a murderer.
Maybe she was a b***
I didn't know Rama
would be such a fool.
- And, you're siding with Vidrohi instead.
- What else?
- Humiliate him like Rama did.
- How can you say that?
Do you know everything that happened?
No, you don't.
A lot of people think
I am wrong, but...
...does that make me wrong too?
You're not wrong for me, Bitti.
So Vidrohi isn't wrong either.
Fine.
- Tea, son.
- Tea won't help anymore, aunty.
Then why did you ask me to make one.
Milk has become so expensive.
I wonder what Bitti
likes about that oaf.
This is a one-sided competition,
brother.
You didn't go to the office today.
I took an off for Vidrohi.
Come on.
There goes your queen.
Wow... amazing.
Come on, let's end this game.
Just to be on the safer side,
you should say 'I love you.
You see, sometime even a rat...
...can create obstacles
in a snake's path.
Sari... but I don't
know how to wear this.
I know how to drape it.
I never imagined that
sari draper will put one on me.
Okay, brother.
Hello.
Vidrohi has opened
sari shop in Bareilly.
- Hello.
- Hello, Listen...
You are fire from job.
Don't come now.
You can't fire me... l fire
you from the post of my boss.
You can keep the money you
owe me and eat a cake.
I should have told
Bitti the truth...
..that I am the author
of Bareilly Ki Barfi.
And I wrote those letters.
Hello son...
You look smarter than
that Vidrohi, brother.
Actually you look smart anyway,
brother.
Whether in a group or solo.
You look handsome from every angle.
You shouldn't make a noise
while eating, it's bad manners.
Quite.
The real fun in eating a malai malpuha
(INDIAN SWEET) is when you make a noise.
Up up chap chap (SOUNDS)
Together now... Chap haa...
Vidrohi.
Does it matter whether
I am a virgin or not?
Virgin? What's that?
And, when I don't even
know what it means...
...how can it bother me?
Cheers to that.
Do you like watching films?
I like watching English films.
- I see...
- Yes.
Do you know English?
I did once...
...but, I didn't like it.
So, I sent it back.
Hold it properly.
The time to say
'I love you is gone.
We just need to wait
and see who Bitti chooses.
Me...
...or him.
You had a problem when I was single.
And now, when I want to get married...
...you still have a problem.
There is no problem, dear.
I never stopped you before, and
I won't stop you now either.
But... think before
you take any decision.
What's to think?
She's marrying a boy.
That's all that matters to me.
Yeah, of course, you'll be happy.
Finally, you're getting
rid of this headache.
I have every reason to be happy.
When your daughter's
staying with you...
...you keep thinking
when she will leave.
And, when she's about to leave...
...you can't stop thinking how
you're going to live without her.
Papa, I won't go if you start crying.
Don't listen to him.
He has tears even
if someone pinches him.
What's wrong?
Fine, I'll get some
tea for you with sugar.
Move, son.
Do you have a cigarette?
That you want to spend
the rest of your life with him.
All he did was write a book.
Well, it did matter before.
But now, it doesn't matter
whether he wrote that book or not.
All that matters now is that
Vidrohi is not a bad guy.
He loves me and...
I'll be happy with him.
Right?
Judging by the way you are, Bitti...
...you'll come across many more
people in life, who'll love you.
Will you marry anyone?
Which people are you talking about?
Do you know how many
times I've been rejected?
Who is willing to marry me?
You've too have known
me for a long time now.
But you didn't fall in love.
I know I've certain faults, Chirag.
But if Vidrohi still likes me,
then what's the problem?
- Why would I have a problem?
- Then...
My only advice is that
you shouldn't be hasty.
What hasty?
Look, I've thought this through,
before making a decision.
And please don't think I
am making a compromise.
Catch.
I told you I'll steal Bitti
from right under your nose.
And I did.
Our engagement's been fixed.
See you.
Regards to your mother.
Stop it...
Let me catch my breath.
I've been holding myself
back for a long time.
If I let go,
you'll have nothing to hold on to.
- Bloody Vidrohi...
- Move.
I'm destined to kill a bearded guy.
So stay away.
You knew... how much I love Bitti.
I loved her a lot.
You used to call her sister-in-law.
Why did you betray me?
Why did you do it?
Did Bitti love you?
Huh?
I loved Rama... but she didn't.
So, what should I do?
Sit in a corner and cry like a woman?
Get this through your skull...
Bitti loves me.
Okay?
Now, find someone else
for your ailing heart.
Because, if anyone now tries
to come between Bitti and me...
...l swear, I will make him pay.
Do show up for the engagement, brother
We haven't called
for the musical band.
Listen...
This attitude you're showing off...
It's my gift to you.
And, when Bitti learns the truth...
...she will kick you out.
I see...
And, who's going to tell Bitti?
Your... best friend, or you?
Who's going to tell her?
Look... if I'm heartbroken
I'll break everyone's heart.
I won't let it happen again.
You will never change, brother.
Fine, go tell her.
Why isn't the light glowing?
- The light glowing, uncle.
- Then, why can't I see it?
It dim light uncle.
Will shine clearly in the night.
I see, it will look better at night.
Then keep them closer,
show I've spent money.
The lights should shine bright, OK.
Put it up there... stop bothering me.
Yes, there.
- Aunty, where is Bitti?
- She must be in the room upstairs.
Why is he looking so dull today?
How am I looking?
Very beautiful.
What's wrong with you?
What can be wrong with me?
You don't look happy.
You look really happy.
I am very happy.
You had something to say?
Chirag.
- Yes, aunty.
- Come down, son. I need you here.
Listen, son. Come here.
Such a pretty ring.
- Isn't it nice?
- Yes.
I really like it a lot.
Give me your hand, son.
Let's see how it looks
on Vidrohi's finger?
Aunty...
- Aunty, why...
- Let me see, son.
Oh my, it looks so pretty.
See, Rama, how does it look?
- It really looks good, aunty.
- It does, doesn't it?
Even I like it a lot.
Now, this is one good
thing that happened.
Have some more.
Come on, son, keep it back in the box.
- What happened?
- It's stuck, aunty.
- How can it be stuck? Turn it around.
- What have you done?
- Turn it around.
- Pull it out, aunty.
- How did it get stuck?
- I'll hold his hand and you pull it out.
- I can't get it out.
- Try to remove it.
- Someone get butter.
- Pull.
- Get some soap.
- What happened?
- What are you doing?
- Pull, aunty.
- The ring is stuck on the finger.
- How can it get stuck?
What's wrong?
Why are you all screaming?
I only wanted to see how it looked,
but I didn't know...
She'll get it out... you go.
Be quiet, she'll do it.
"You're untouched by
the norms of the world."
"You're the grace in my eyes."
"Every breath I take..."
"...and in all my dreams..."
"l see your prints everywhere I look."
"O wanderer... I am in love..."
"Love with you."
"You're like the shadow
of a soaring bird."
"The boat that floats carelessly."
"You cannot settle down..."
"because,
you're like the caravan of a nomad."
"l am treading... on the footsteps,
you've left behind."
"Wondering whether we'll ever meet."
"O wanderer... I am in love..."
"Love with you."
What did sister-in-law say?
I couldn't gather
the courage to tell her.
Why?
She's very happy with Vidrohi.
How could I break her heart?
I was very selfish, Munna.
I couldn't see anything beyond
my happiness alone.
Well...
Love taught me to
be happy in other's happiness.
And Vidrohi's not a bad guy either.
You're not a villain, brother.
How are you, brother?
Fine.
Sorry, man.
It was entirely my fault.
I troubled you without a reason.
It's okay.
Here.
What's this?
I've written something... for Bitti.
It's from you...
...because you're a really bad writer.
Read this out at your engagement.
She will like it.
Please come to my engagement, brother.
It will make me really happy.
I don't have any choice now.
Even today, there's not a
single dull moment in Mishra Sadan.'
'Poor Romeo... is making sweets.'
- Listen...
- Greetings, uncle.
Congratulation.
Chirag.
Pour some milk in that coffee machine.
- Yes, uncle.
- Look here...
- Hello, sister. Hello...
- Bless you son..
- Upstairs, go on...
- Yes.
Look here,
your friend is making sweets.
Go... go.
Come, son.
- The function is upstairs.
- There's a problem, brother.
What's wrong with your voice.
That's the problem.
My mother made tea
from curdled milk...
- And this is what happened.
- What now?
- Now, who's going to read this letter?
- Who?
- Munna, you read it.
- No...
- You read it then.
- How can I read it?
What are you saying?
Hello... Thank you for coming.
Be happy son.
- You read it.
- Let's go upstairs.
Please read it.
- Please read it. Brother.
- Fill it with clarified butter.
Bitti...
Look now, your electricity
department is betraying us.
Lallan, coffee.
- Coffee...
- Here she is.
Papa
- Wow... so beautiful.
- That way, dear. That way.
- You're looking so beautiful, my child.
- That way?
- Let's go.
Sit here.
- Sit here.
- Yes
So beautiful.
The curly hair looks so nice.
- Don't touch it.
- Don't touch her hair, you'll ruin it.
Excuse me...
my dear brothers...
- ...and sisters, except for one.
- What's wrong with his voice?
- Don't know.
- Mothers and Fathers...
On the auspicious
occasion of my engagement...
...I've written something for you,
Bitti, straight from my heart.
But if I read it out in this voice...
...then, you'll all get depressed.
So, my best friend Chirag
will read it out for me.
Come on, Chirag.
- I'll go sit there.
- Yeah...
- It's hard to hear anything from here.
- He's written a letter... for you.
Come sister-in-law
- Sit here...
Move aside.
"Bareilly Ki Barfi... Bitti!"
"You must be wondering..."
"I've already written
so much about you..."
"...that what do I have left to say."
You wouldn't have
the slightest clue..."
"...but I've enough to say about you
which can last an entire lifetime."
"Some think you're short-tempered."
"Some think you're spoilt."
"Your mother amusingly says that..."
"...when you wander out at nights,
you look like a witch."
"Sometimes you're odd..."
"...and sometimes
you're very interesting."
"But I swear,
I like everything about you."
Oh, God. What just happened?
Oh no, not another power-cut.
He was reading
such a romantic letter.
See...
There's a power cut
in the entire city...
...but power will be
restored soon enough.
We regret the inconvenience caused.
You're very strange.
Every time you laugh,
your front tooth's visible.
Even your gums light up.
Every time you cry,
your nose starts running.
You get happy without a reason...
...and lose your temper
over trivial things.
It's not easy to love you.
But, it's harder to not love you.
You're like this light in my life.
And no one in this world,
can love you as much as I do.
Let's make a bet.
And, if l lose... you
can take anything you want.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Come, Vidrohi.
How long are you going to hide it?
I know who wrote Bareilly Ki Barfi.
Along with all those letters.
I know everything.
But, who told you?
Munna?
I am not a traitor, brother.
I am on your side.
I don't know.
Yes, son,
I just found out a few days ago.
And we started preparing since then.
Then...
Vidrohi.
Vidrohi got emotional.
When I tried to console him,...
...he spilled out everything.
'Chirag is the author
of Bareilly Ki Barfi'.
'These two got me in this mess.'
You could've told
me if you already knew.
But I didn't know...
...whether you really love me,
or maybe because...
...you see Babli in me.
And it was very important
for me to find out.
Hence I played this charade.
Through Mr. Bishnoi we booked...
Oh no...
'Cheers to that.'
You didn't fall in love with me.
I tested you at every step.
But you passed every test.
I troubled you a lot, didn't I?
- Sorry.
- Don't say sorry.
Bitti, here you go.
Adorn it.
But, I don't have one.
I didn't come prepared.
- What will he adorn?
- Brother Chirag.
Look at him.
Like I said...
Bitti's my sister-in-law.
I will slap you..
- I troubled you a lot.
- It's alright.
Adorn it.
I'm going to frame this.
I'll never forget this ever.
Papa.
But this didn't fit.
We took your measurement
yesterday, son.
You guys really made
me dance to your tunes.
Coffee's here...
There's never a power
cut when you need one.
'A story with a name
like 'Barfi' (SWEET)...'
'...will always have a happy ending.'
How is it?
Spicy.
They are now made for each other.'
'Oh... we completely forgot
to offer you sweets.'
'Now Vidrohi explains English
films to Rama in his own style.'
'But unfortunately, in theaters,
the corner seat is a rarity....
'...when their mother's
sticking around.'
'Chirag, Munna, and Vidrohi...'
'...have become more
than just best friends.'
'Well, there's just Mr.
Mishra left now.'
'During the day,
he listens to his wife...'
'...and at night,
he talks to the fan.'
'If you visit Bareilly again...'
'...then, instead of wasting
time looking for the earrings...'
'...opt for 'Barfi'
(SWEETS) instead.'
"Your earrings make
my heart skip a beat."
"When you shake the waist,
it steals millions of hearts."
"Stop taunting me...
Don't be a wise guy."
"l am not Juliet,
And you're not my Romeo."
"O Sweety..."
"O Sweety your drama,
creates a stir."
"This is unfair."
"Believe it or not,
we're crazy about you..."
"Listen O sweetheart,
we're your beloved."
"DJ."
"Crazy"
"Don't make a commotion..."
"...everyone's watching."
"What do you get
from making a scene."
"Don't ignore me...
I am not useless."
"Teach me the language of love."
"Stop taunting me...
Don't be a wise guy."
"l am not Juliet,
And you're not my Romeo."
"O Sweety..."
"O Sweety your drama,
creates a stir."
"This is unfair."
"Believe it or not,
we're crazy about you..."
"Listen O sweetheart,
we're your beloved."
"Abracadabra...
my beloved's so handsome."
"Always dressed smartly,
whether it's Delhi or Agra."